Privacy Policy
==============

GoToQuiz.com is committed to maintaining high standards of privacy for its visitors. This document describes the ways in which we respect visitor privacy.

### Information GoToQuiz stores:

Our server logs the visitor's IP address and certain browser headers as part of the standard logging proccess that most web sites follow. This data is stored only in log form and is used to generate aggregate reports on visitor use of the site. Information such as real names and e-mail addresses are not collected by simply visiting GoToQuiz.com, and in fact are not possible to collect without a visitor actually volunteering that information.

When taking quizzes at GoToQuiz.com, if you have not created a GoToQuiz account, no quiz results are linked to you in any way unless you have opted in. Answers to some questions may be logged only to generate aggregate reports, which may be made public. This data is anonymized. The quiz results of users with GoToQuiz accounts are saved and may be deleted upon request. Saved results are displayed to the quiz-makers, and are not used for marketing purposes.

We may collect personal information volunteered by the visitor through the use of HTML forms, and this might include surveys, site registrations, or other form posts.

### What GoToQuiz does with stored information:

Any information that is volunteered by a visitor is not shared with any third parties unless the visitor has given explicit permission to do so ("opt-in"). Internally, this information may be used to make personalized recommendations (such as quiz recommendations) or to adjust the advertisements that are shown.

### How GoToQuiz uses cookies:

Using GoToQuiz.com may result in a cookie being set, which is used to "remember" you from page to page. This is the essential function of HTTP cookies. In this case, it allows you to log in to a GoToQuiz account as well as for GoToQuiz.com to make personalized recommendations and show more accurate advertising offers to you during your visit.

It is possible for you to disable or modify the cookie feature in your browser by consulting your browser's "help" screen, looking up cookies, and following the directions. Be aware that disabling cookies will likely disable certain functionality on the sites you visit.

### Third party advertisements appearing on GoToQuiz:

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to GoToQuiz.com, ad server companies may collect information such as your browser headers, IP address, whether you have Flash or javascript enabled, and clickstream. Advertisers may use web beacons or cookies to collect this information (which is in turn used to tailor advertisements to you), as well as monitor clicks and credit commissions. The following information describes Google's privacy disclosures:

* Google and its advertising partners use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to GoToQuiz users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising [opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
* Google may use third party ad networks to show advertising on GoToQuiz. You can find a list of these [here](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149).
* Users may visit the web sites of these ad networks to opt out of cookies or other means of tracking. Alternatively, users may opt out of multiple ad networks by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Additional Information: Google's DoubleClick uses cookies to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads displayed will be chosen based on your previous browsing history. This does not rely on personally identifying information. You can opt-out of this specific ad serving on all sites that use it by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart\_adserving.aspx

You can view Google's privacy policy here: [http://www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

You can view Commission Junction's privacy policy here: [http://www.cj.com/privacy.jsp](http://www.cj.com/privacy.jsp)

### Changes to this document:

From time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated reasons not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will update this document to reflect the changes. It is your responsibility to check this document for updates. Changes to our privacy policy will not retroactively affect any data collected. GoToQuiz makes a good faith effort to let users know how information collected will be used on the very form pages where it is collected. However, this document is the ultimate authority on user privacy at GoToQuiz.

### Contact:

If this policy is unclear in any way, you may request clarification by sending an e-mail to our e-mail address.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, or if you want stored data about you removed, you may contact us with your concerns at our e-mail address.

Our e-mail address can be found on our [contact page](https://www.gotoquiz.com/contact.html).
